seenon.com 2009-11-17

# Privacy Policy | SeenON!

SeenON! is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that all customer information be kept strictly confidential. As a condition to using the Service, you agree to the terms of the SeenON!™ Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time. SeenON! will not sell, trade, or disclose your personal information to any third parties. Under no circumstances will personal information be shared with any third party without your permission. If you have opted in to receive email notifications, SeenON! may send you notices about products & services, promotions, or contests from SeenON! or our promotional partners. SeenON!™ understands that privacy is important to you. You do, however, agree that SeenON!™ may monitor, edit or disclose your personal information, including the content of your emails, if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order), or as otherwise provided in these Terms of Use and the SeenON!™ Privacy Policy. Personal information collected by SeenON!™ may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which parent company [Delivery Agent, Inc. ](http://www.deliveryagent.com/ "Delivery Agent - Making Entertainment Shoppable")or its agents maintain facilities. By using SeenON!™, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. We recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly and are committed to doing so.
